> > Brian Holt: 现在，我们做了这些，让我们做这个，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So now, that we've
done all of this, let's go make this,
我们现在就去做吧
let's do the render now, right?
所以我要做的第一件事
So what I'm gonna do,
the first thing we're gonna
say 为 ( this.state.loads ) ，然后返回 &lt;h1&gt; 装入。
say is if (this.state.loading)
then return an &lt;h1&gt; of loading.
> > 布莱恩 - 霍尔特: 现在，我们可以把这些都挺漂亮的，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Now, we could make this all
pretty and have like a nice spinner and
都是这样的对吧
everything like that, right?
但我要把它留给你的想象对吧
But I'll leave that to your imagination,
right?
现在我们只会展示一个加载指示器对吧
For now, we're just gonna show
a loading indicator, right?
>> Brian Holt: 如果不是 true ，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: If that's not true,
那我们要做什么， >> Brian Holt:
then what we're gonna do,
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Is I'm gonna do
这就是我喜欢这样做的原因
some destructuring in here,
because this is how I prefer to do it.
但这只是我的首选我要说的是
But this is just my preference here,
I'm gonna say const {animal,
品种，位置，描述，名称} = this.state。
breed, location, description,
name} = this.state.
> > 布莱恩 - 霍尔特: 好的，现在，我把所有这些都拉出来了。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay, now, that I've
pulled all of those out of this.state,
我要在一个 &lt;div&gt;里回话
I'm gonna say return inside of a &lt;div&gt;,
and
&lt;h1&gt; 使用 {name，我在此处必须有两个 div 。
&lt;h1&gt; with the {name,
I have to have two divs here.
两个 divs ， &lt;div className="details"&gt; 结束。
Two divs,
&lt;div className="details"&gt; that to the end.
> > Brian Holt: 在那里，我得到了那个卷曲的支架，好的。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Up right there,
I got that curly brace, okay.
所以请确保你有两个潜水夫
So, yeah,
make sure you have two divs here.
我觉得为了造型的目的我也得这样做，所以你们都没做过
I think I had to do that for styling
purposes, so none of you have ever done
那之前就放一个随机的 div ，这样你就能比较好吗 ?
that before, just put a random div,
just so you could style it better?
好吧好吧只是我
Okay, good, it's just me.
>> 演讲者 2: [LAUGH] >> Brian Holt:
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: [LAUGH]
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: All right, instead of that,
放了个 h2 然后我就把这些花括号都放了
put an h2, and
then I'm gonna put these curly braces, and
我要在这里做同样的仪式动物
I'm gonna do same sort of ritual here,
animal.
>> Brian Holt: [品种] >> Brian Holt: [位置]。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: [breed]
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: [location].
>> Brian Holt: 好的。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay.
>> Brian Holt: 在此情况下，我们将放置一个 " 采用 [名称]" 按钮。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Under that we're gonna
put a button that says Adopt [name].
> > Brian Holt: 然后我们会 &lt;p&gt;，然后在其中，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And then we're gonna &lt;p&gt;,
and then inside of that,
我们会把你的描述
we'll put the description.
>> Brian Holt: 因此，此处没有挂钩，您必须使用 this.state 和 set 状态。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So again, no hooks in here,
you have to use this.state and set state.
不使用更新状态或设置状态或设置位置，
Instead of using update state or
set state or set location,
就像我们用钩子对吧
like we do with hooks, right?
我们有一个功能相当于一个国家
We have one function that
corresponds to one piece of state,
你把这个 .setState 都用在哪里
you just use this .setState everywhere.
这样你就会非常熟悉这种设定状态。
So you'll get very familiar
with this type of set state.
现在我很努力地避免用这种老方法
Now, I'm trying really hard to refrain
from calling this the old way of doing
因为我觉得这会永远存在
things, because I think this
is going to be around forever.
我觉得钩子和课都要留下来
I think that hooks and
classes are around to stay.
我们没有任何迹象表明课程会被弃用。
We have no indication that
classes are gonna get deprecated.
我个人的意见，这其实是一个很好的 API ，还是这个
I'm of the personal opinion, this actually
a really great API and this is still
一个有效的写作方式和一个应该在你的工具箱里的工具
a valid way to write react and definitely
a tool that should be in your toolbox.
>> Brian Holt: 但我会说这绝对容易
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: But
I will say that it is definitely easier
是从钩子开始的对吧
to start with hooks, right?
它只是功能和使用状态，所以现在让我们看看这是否有效。
It's just functions and use state,
so let's go see if this works now.
这不起作用，因为细节不是真实的地方，
This won't work,
because details one is not a real place,
让我们在这里点击胖子 Slim
so let's go click on Fat Boy Slim here.
" 胖男孩 Slim " 在美国的斯坦伍德 ( Stanwood ) 。
There you go, Fat Boy Slim is
a rottweiler in Stanwood, Washington.
他的天性和玩伴的方式
And his sweet nature and
and has playful ways.
>> Brian Holt: 然后我们在这里再做一个按钮
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And then we'll make
a button here in just a second that you
实际上可以进入收养的网页
actually be able to go
to the adoption page,
如果你也想领养动物
if you do want to adopt
the animal as well.